Guide to the John G. Brady Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1896-1917; Series III; 1' (3 boxes)
  - ARTICLES AND SPEECHES
    - "A Condition of Mind"; "Conservation in Alaska"; "Coal Lands in Alaska"; in Commerce and Industries Magazine, 1911 Oct (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - "Alaska" (abstract), TMs, 1913 Apr 7 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - "Alaska: Size and Resources," TMs, 1913 May (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - "Citizenship for the Alaskan Natives," AMs, TMs, c. 1913 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - "Prospectus for a Lumber Company to be Organized at Sitka," AMs, c. 1913 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - "The Cruise of the Rose in June, 1878," AMs, TMs, 1915 Dec (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - "Digressions in the Mining History of Alaska," AMs, TMs, c. 1915 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - "The First Attempt of Miners to Cross Chilcoot Pass," TMs, c. 1915 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - "Indian Law in Sitka in 1878," TMs, c. 1915 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - "Katleean's Attempt at Sitka in 1879," AMs, TMs, c. 1915 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - "My Visit to Washington in the Spring of 1879," AMs, TMs, c. 1915 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - "The Fiftieth Anniversary of the Treaty Ceding Russian America to the United States," AMs, TMs, c. 1917 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - "Alaska," AMs, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - "Alaska," TMs, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Alaska and its resources: miscellaneous AMs and TMs (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - "Alaska, Error and Neglect," AMs, TMs (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - "Alaska the Key to the Orient," AMs (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - "Alaska: The New-found Resources," AMs, TMs (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - "Alaskan Natives," AMs, TMs, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Alaskan natives: miscellaneous AMs and TMs (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - "Alaskan Short Stories: The First Advance of Miners into Alaska," AMs, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - "Alaska's Great Industry," AMs (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - "Alaska's Ice," AMs, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - "Comedy of the Organic Act, May 17, 1884," AMs, TMs, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - "Conditions in Alaska," AMs (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - "The Disposal of the Public Domain and Tomfoolery with Alaska" (outline), AMs, TMs (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - "Historic Sitka," AMs, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - "Home Rule for Alaska," AMs, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - "The Mineral Wealth of Alaska" (version 1), AMs, TMs, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - "The Mineral Wealth of Alaska" (version 2), AMs, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - "Mining in Alaska," AMs, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - "Mr. John C. Calhoun and the Public Lands," AMs, TMs (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - "The Natives of Alaska," AMs, TMs, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - "Opportunities for a Poor Man or a Man of Moderate Means in Agricultural Alaska," TMs, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - "Our Commercial Relations with the Orient," TMs, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - "The Present Status of the Alaskan Natives," AMs, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - "Reindeer in Alaska," AMs (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - "Rev. Sheldon Jackson, D.D., A Progressive Missionary," TMs (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - "Mrs. A. R. McFarland," TMs
    - "The Story of Mining in Alaska," AMs (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - "Tomfoolery with Alaska" (version 2), TMs, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Miscellaneous AMs and TMs (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Miscellaneous AMs and TMs (fragments) (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - RESEARCH NOTES
    - Chinese-American Trading Company, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - "H. W. Elliott's Report", n.d. (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Public domain, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - "Purchase of Alaska", n.d. (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - "Secret instructions to a Russian navigator", n.d. (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Seward, William H., n.d. (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Statehood, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 66-67)
    - "Stories", n.d. (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 69-70)
    - Notebooks, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 71-75)
- Official, Legal and Financial Papers, 1874-1920; Series IV; 0.5' (1 box)
  This series is arranged by form of material, and chronologically within folders.
  - OFFICIAL PAPERS
    - Documents, 1888-1901 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Legal briefs and agreements, 1884-1914 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Thanksgiving proclamations, 1892-99 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Thanksgiving proclamations, 1900-02 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Thanksgiving proclamations, 1903-05 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Financial records, 1889-1914 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Receipts for Indian Police service, 1891-99 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Copy of first map of Juneau, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - LEGAL PAPERS
    - Contracts and agreements, 1886-1913 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Legal briefs, 1885-1901 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Plot maps of Brady property, 1900 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Plot maps of Hugh Patton property, 1900 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Business and industrial records, 1884-1913 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Estate distribution decree, 1920 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Burial permit, 1918
  - FINANCIAL PAPERS
    - Life insurance policies and receipts, 1896-1914 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Bills and receipts, 1874-1915 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Personal and Family Papers, 1876-1924; Series V; 1' (2 boxes) + 1 broadside
  This series is arranged by individual, then by form of materials. Unidentified papers are located at the end of the series.
  - JOHN G. BRADY
    - Articles about John G. Brady, 1880-1898 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Articles about John G. Brady, 1899 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Articles about John G. Brady, 1900-03 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Articles about John G. Brady, 1904-18, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Articles about John G. Brady, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - S.M. Bemiss, "John Green Brady and the Quest for Home Rule in Alaska" (student paper), 1976 Nov (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Biographical notes (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - "Report on Brady Manuscript," TMs, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Certificates, 1877-1900 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Certificates, 1901-07 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Certificates, diplomas, and commissions, 1874-1917 (Box 41 (Broadside))
    - Drawings, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Programs, 1874-99 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Programs, 1900-04 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Programs, 1905-22, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Calling cards, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Invitations and complimentary tickets, 1887-1905 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Memorabilia: Masonic apron and Governor's pen (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - ELIZABETH (PATTON) BRADY
    - Writings: "The Government Community School at Sitka, Alaska", 1917 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Diary: first trip to Alaska, 1886 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Diary: trip to St. Louis World's Fair, 1904 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Notebooks: letters written during first year in Sitka, 1887 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Notebooks: Thlingit language and lore (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - MARY B. BRADY
    - Writings: (collaborator), "Young Americans at Play in Foreign Lands", 1921 Aug 3 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Writings: "How Students Can Borrow Money with Character as Security," in The Independent, 1924 Jan 5 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - JOHN G. BRADY, JR.
    - Diary, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - CASSIA PATTON
    - Papers on Alaskan Society of History and Ethnology, 1892-95 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - UNIDENTIFIED
    - Notebook and notes (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Notebook, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Printed Material, 1867-1937; Series VI; 2.5' (6 boxes)
  This series is organized in six subseries: organizational publications; articles; general printed material; newspapers and periodicals; newspaper clippings; and books. Organizational publications are arranged alphabetically by the organization's name. Articles about Alaska are arranged chronologically. General printed material is arranged by form--e.g., leaflets, pictures, maps. Newspapers and periodicals are arranged alphabetically by title, then chronologically. Newspaper clippings which the collector had grouped by subject have been arranged alphabetically by subject heading; miscellaneous clippings not grouped by subject have been arranged chronologically by year. Books are arranged chronologically.
  - ORGANIZATIONAL PUBLICATIONS
    - Alaska Bureau of Publicity: leaflets and brochures, 1917-21 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Alaska, Department of Education
      - "School Laws of the Territory of Alaska", 1919 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - "Report of the Commissioner of Education for 1918, 1919 and 1920" (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - "Report of the Commissioner of Education for 1921 and 1922" (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - "Manual and Course of Study for the High Schools of Alaska", 1922 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - "Manual and Course of Study for the Elementary Schools of Alaska", 1923 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - "Historical Sketch of Alaska", 1923 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Alaska, Governor's Office: "Alaska, Outline of Its History and a Summary of Its Resources", 1924-25 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Alaska Road Commission: "Twenty-First Annual Report", 1925 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Alaska Steamship Company: "Alaska Totem Poles", 1906 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Alaska-Yukon-Pacific Exposition: publications, 1909 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Anchorage Chamber of Commerce: publications, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Anchorage Woman's Club: year book, 1923-24 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Episcopal Church, Department of Missions: "The Borderland of the Pole", 1921 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Juneau Chamber of Commerce: brochures, map (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.: Mission Board publications, 1909-23, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Pacific Coast Steamship Company: "The Alaska Indian Mythology" (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Seattle Chamber of Commerce, Alaska Bureau: publications, 1916-22 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Southeastern Alaska Fair: "Official Premium List", n.d. (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Taku River Company: "The Call of the Northland" (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Tanana Dredging Company: prospectus, map, brochure, c. 1910 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - United States Government publications
      - Leaflets, 1875, 1900 (Box 16, Folder 22)
      - "Introduction to the Study of Indian Languages", 1877 (Box 16, Folder 23)
      - "Grammar and Vocabulary of the Hlingit Language of Southeastern Alaska", 1905 (Box 16, Folder 24)
      - "Reports Relating to Alaskan Seal Fisheries", 1908 (Box 16, Folder 25)
      - "General Information Regarding the Territory of Alaska", 1914 (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - School Life, 1918, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 27)
      - "General Information Regarding the Territory of Alaska", 1919 (Box 17, Folder 28-29)
      - Alaskan Engineering Commission reports, 1919-20 (Box 17, Folder 30)
      - "Report of the Alaska Agricultural Experiment Stations, 1919", 1920 (Box 17, Folder 31)
      - "Reindeer in Alaska", 1922 (Box 17, Folder 32)
      - "Fisheries in Alaska", 1922 (Box 17, Folder 33)
      - "General Information Regarding the Territory of Alaska", 1923 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Western Alaska Fair Association: "First Annual Fair, Official Premium List", 1924 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - ARTICLES ABOUT ALASKA
    - General, 1885-1923, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Education and welfare work, 1909-24, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - "Alaska a Land of Great Promise," by Scott C. Bone, 1922 Sep (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - "Alaska, the Misunderstood," by Sherman Rogers, 1922 Dec 6 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - "The 'Beautiful, Fruitful Wilderness' of Alaska", 1923 Aug 11 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - "Seward's Folly," by Edison Marshall, 1924 May 7 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - "The Passing Alaskan," by Barrett Willoughby, 1926 May (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - GENERAL PRINTED MATERIAL
    - Postcards, leaflets, advertisements, booklets, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Pictures, 1898-1914, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Maps of Alaska: general, 1917-21 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Maps of Alaska: local survey maps, 1882-1923 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - NEWSPAPERS AND PERIODICALS
    - The Alaska Daily Empire (Juneau), 1925 Jan-Apr (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - The Alaska Daily Empire (Juneau), 1925 May (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - The Alaska Daily Empire (Juneau), 1925 Jun 1-26 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - The Alaska Daily Empire (Juneau), 1925 Jun 27-30 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - The Alaska Daily Empire (Juneau), 1925 Jul, Nov (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - The Alaska Daily Empire (Juneau), 1937 Apr 24 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - The Alaska Fisherman (Juneau), 1923 Feb, Apr (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - The Alaska Fisherman (Ketchikan), 1924 Jan (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Alaska Forum (Rampart), 1905 Jan-Feb (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Alaska Herald (San Francisco), 1872-73 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Alaska Herald (San Francisco), 1874-75, 1880 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - The Alaska Miner (Juneau), 1897 Sep 4 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - The Alaska Weekly (Seattle), 1923 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - The Alaska Weekly (Seattle), 1924 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - The Alaska Weekly (Seattle), 1925 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - The Alaskan (Sitka), 1887, 1897 (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - The Alaskan (Sitka), 1899-1906 (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - Anchorage Daily Alaskan, 1924 Aug-Sep (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Anchorage Daily Times, 1924 Sep (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - Anchorage Daily Times, 1925 Mar 30-Apr 5 (Box 19, Folder 66)
    - Anchorage Daily Times, 1925 Apr 6-10 (Box 19, Folder 67)
    - Boston Alaskan, 1906 Aug (Box 19, Folder 68)
    - Christian Herald (New York), 1895 Jan 9 (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - Columbia Spectator (New York), 1920 Aug 13 (Box 19, Folder 70)
    - Daily Alaska Dispatch (Juneau), 1900 Feb 7 (Box 19, Folder 71)
    - The Gold Fields (St. Louis, World's Fair), 1904 Jun (Box 19, Folder 72)
    - The Hyder Silver Dollar, 1922 May 4 (Box 19, Folder 73)
    - The Indian's Friend (New York), 1925 Mar (Box 19, Folder 74)
    - The Metlakahtlan (Metlakahtla), 1888-90 (Box 19, Folder 75)
    - The North Star (Sitka), 1889-96 (Box 19, Folder 76)
    - The Sitka Sun, 1920 Nov (Box 19, Folder 77)
    - The Sitka Tribune, 1924 Jul, Nov (Box 19, Folder 78)
    - The Sun (New York), 1917 Jan 10 (Box 19, Folder 79)
    - Victoria Daily Times (Victoria, B.C.), 1897 Nov 27 (Box 19, Folder 80)
  - NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS
    - Agriculture, livestock, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 81)
    - Business and industry (Box 19, Folder 82)
    - Education, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 83)
    - Fisheries, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 84)
    - Forestry, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 85)
    - Furs, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 86)
    - Glacier Bay, Juneau, Seattle, Sitka, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 87)
    - Government, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 88)
    - Harding, Warren G., n.d. (Box 20, Folder 89)
    - Historical articles, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 90)
    - Mining, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 91)
    - Native Alaskans, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 92)
    - Natural resources, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 93)
    - Railroad, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 94)
    - Roads, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 95)
    - Social life, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 96)
    - Social organizations, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 97)
    - Tourists, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 98)
    - Transportation, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 99)
    - Wildlife, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 100)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1878-97 (Box 20, Folder 101)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1898-99 (Box 20, Folder 102)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1900-02 (Box 20, Folder 103)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1903 (Box 20, Folder 104)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1905-06 (Box 20, Folder 105)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1913-17 (Box 20, Folder 106)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 107)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1921 (Box 20, Folder 108)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1922 (Box 20, Folder 109)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1923 (Box 21, Folder 110-12)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1924 (Box 21, Folder 113-14)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1925 (Box 21, Folder 115-18)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1926, 1930, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 119)
  - BOOKS
    - New Testament (American Bible Society editions), 1867, 1869 (Box 21, Folder 120)
    - Bible (in English), and New Testament (in Greek) (Box 21, Folder 121)
- Photographs, 1870-1925; Series VII; 8' (18 Boxes)
  This series is organized in six subseries: paper prints; photograph albums; glass negatives; negatives; printing block; and glass lantern slides. The photographic paper prints are arranged alphabetically by subject, and chronologically under each heading. The two photograph albums are arranged chronologically. Glass negatives are arranged by subject, and all other negatives are arranged alphabetically by subject, then chronologically. There is one printing block, following the negatives. Glass lantern slides are arranged alphabetically by subject, with no specific organization within subject headings. See the Appendix for a list of photographers and indexes to the photographs of T. W. Ingersoll and I. W. Taber.
  - PAPER PRINTS
    - Agriculture, 1890-1912, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Animals
      - Fish and seals, 1898, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Musk ox, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous, c. 1886, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Boats: native Alaskan, 1901, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Brady, John G.
      - Portraits, 1900-09 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Family, group portraits, 1895-1918, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 8-13)
      - Family, individual portraits, 1891, 1900 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Garden, 1899-1906, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 15-16)
      - Home, 1886-1910 (Box 22, Folder 17-19)
    - Buildings
      - Miscellaneous, 1890-1902 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Miscellaneous, 1904-1918 (Box 22, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 22)
      - Native Alaskan, 1890 (Box 22, Folder 23)
      - Native Alaskan, 1898-1902 (Box 22, Folder 24)
      - Russian Blockhouse, Sitka, 1897-1912 (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - Sitka Trading Company, c. 1900 (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - Postcards, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Churches
      - Miscellaneous, 1898-1901 (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 29)
      - Greek Orthodox, Sitka, 1886-1902, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 30-33)
      - St. Peter's by the Sea, Sitka, 1900-25 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Crafts: native Alaskan, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 35-36)
    - Crafts: native Alaskan: postcards, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Dogsleds, 1907-19, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Fishing
      - Herring Fishing, 1901, 1918, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 39)
      - Native Alaskans preparing fish, 1907 (Box 23, Folder 40)
      - Salmon and other fishing, 1895-1903 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Forests and trees, 1908-13 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Graves, 1874, 1900 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Graves: native Alaskan, 1890-98, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Horse transportation, 1897-1909 (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Hunting
      - Fur animals, 1888-1903, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 46)
      - Native Alaskans preparing furs, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 47)
      - Whales, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 48)
      - Postcards, 1910, 1918 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Industries: miscellaneous, 1906, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Landscapes, 1890 or before (Box 23, Folder 51-52)
    - Landscapes, 1896 (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Landscapes, 1897 (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - Landscapes, 1898 (Box 24, Folder 55)
    - Landscapes, 1899 (Box 24, Folder 56)
    - Landscapes, 1900 (Box 24, Folder 57-59)
    - Landscapes, 1901 (Box 24, Folder 60)
    - Landscapes, 1904 (Box 24, Folder 61)
    - Landscapes, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 62)
    - Landscapes, 1907 (Box 24, Folder 63)
    - Landscapes, 1910-23 (Box 24, Folder 64)
    - Landscapes (Box 24, Folder 65-69)
    - Landscapes (Box 24, Folder 70-71)
    - Landscapes (Box 24, Folder 72)
    - Lumber industry, 1913, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 73)
    - Mining industry, 1887-1901 (Box 24, Folder 74)
    - Mining industry, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 75)
    - Mining industry, 1908-18 (Box 24, Folder 76)
    - Mining industry (Box 24, Folder 77)
    - Portraits of groups
      - Native Alaskans, 1880-1905, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 78)
      - Native Alaskan children, 1890-1907 (Box 24, Folder 79)
      - Native Alaskan children, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 80-81)
      - Native Alaskan couples, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 82)
      - Native Alaskan families, 1898-1900 (Box 24, Folder 83)
      - Native Alaskan families, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 84-85)
      - Native Alaskan men, 1870-98 (Box 25, Folder 86)
      - Native Alaskan men, 1900-02 (Box 25, Folder 87)
      - Native Alaskan men, 1904-08 (Box 25, Folder 88)
      - Native Alaskan men, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 89)
      - Native Alaskan men: postcard, 1904 (Box 25, Folder 90)
      - Native Alaskan school children, 1886-1906 (Box 25, Folder 91)
      - Native Alaskan school children, 1918, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 92)
      - Native Alaskan school children: postcards, 1906-18 (Box 25, Folder 93)
      - Native Alaskan women, 1890-95 (Box 25, Folder 94)
      - Native Alaskan women, 1896-1900 (Box 25, Folder 95)
      - Native Alaskan women: postcard, c. 1908 (Box 25, Folder 96)
      - White, identified, 1886-87 (Box 25, Folder 97)
      - White, identified, 1892-1900 (Box 25, Folder 98)
      - White, identified, 1901-05, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 99)
      - White, identified, 1906-07, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 100)
      - White school children, 1895, 1918 (Box 25, Folder 101)
      - White, unidentified, c. 1890 (Box 25, Folder 102)
      - White, unidentified, 1897-1904 (Box 25, Folder 103)
      - White, unidentified, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 104)
      - White, unidentified, 1907 (Box 25, Folder 105)
      - White, unidentified, 1911-17 (Box 25, Folder 106)
      - White, unidentified, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 107)
    - Portraits of individuals (Box 26)
      - Native Alaskan, identified, 1880-1916 (Box 26, Folder 108)
      - Native Alaskan, identified, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 109)
      - Native Alaskan, unidentified, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 110-11)
      - Native Alaskan, unidentified: postcard, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 112)
      - Oriental, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 113)
      - Whites, some identified, 1898-1901 (Box 26, Folder 114)
      - Whites, some identified, 1902-12 (Box 26, Folder 115)
    - Railroads, 1900-03 (Box 26, Folder 116)
    - Railroads, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 117)
    - Railroads, 1907 (Box 26, Folder 118-22)
    - Railroads, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 123)
    - Road transportation, 1901, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 124)
    - Ships, 1886-89 (Box 26, Folder 125)
    - Ships, 1890-97 (Box 26, Folder 126)
    - Ships, 1900 (Box 26, Folder 127)
    - Ships, 1901 (Box 26, Folder 128-29)
    - Ships, 1902-06 (Box 26, Folder 130)
    - Ships, 1907-10 (Box 26, Folder 131)
    - Ships, 1911 (Box 26, Folder 132)
    - Ships, 1915 (Box 26, Folder 133)
    - Ships, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 134-37)
    - Ship postcards, 1907-18 (Box 26, Folder 138)
    - Social activities, 1886-98 (Box 26, Folder 139)
    - Social activities, 1900-10 (Box 26, Folder 140)
    - Social activities, 1911 (Box 26, Folder 141)
    - Social activities, 1912 (Box 26, Folder 142)
    - Social activities, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 143)
    - Social activities, Native Alaskan, 1890-98 (Box 27, Folder 144)
    - Social activities, Native Alaskan, 1900-01 (Box 27, Folder 145)
    - Social activities, Native Alaskan, 1905-06 (Box 27, Folder 146)
    - Social activities, Postcards, 1910, 1912 (Box 27, Folder 147)
    - Totems, c. 1880 (Box 27, Folder 148)
    - Totems, 1890-1901 (Box 27, Folder 149-50)
    - Totems, 1901 (Box 27, Folder 151-52)
    - Totems, 1902-18 (Box 27, Folder 153)
    - Totems, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 154)
    - Totems, Postcards, 1902-16 (Box 27, Folder 155)
    - Towns
      - Anchorage, 1880 (Box 27, Folder 156)
      - Chena, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 157)
      - Cordova, 1906 (Box 27, Folder 158)
      - Fairbanks, 1922, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 159)
      - Juneau, 1901, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 160)
      - Karlak, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 161)
      - Ketchikan, 1900 (Box 27, Folder 162)